John Geronimo

Junior Frontend Developer/Web Developer

Resourceful team member with a proven history of reliability and excellent work. Driven and proven successful at achieving established targets and team goals. Dynamic and creative frontend developer with experience in producing code with great quality.

Work History

2019-07 -2020-06

Development Team Member (Internship)

Auckland University of Technology (AUT) - Ruru Artisans Website

- Develop WordPress Theme for the website
- Edit website layout through coding and plugins
- Create and add content for website pages

2012-01 -2012-10

Delivery

New Zealand Herald

• Delivering news papers

2015-09 -

Work Personnel

2016-04

Texas Chicken

Preparing/Cooking Chicken, Cleaning of work area,
 Sorting of Resources, Working under pressure

2016-07 -2020-05

Committed Student Leader (Volunteer)

Auckland Student Life

 Weekly surveys, Lead bible group studies, Run welcoming events, Leadership, Time management, Communication

Education

2016-06 - Bachelor of Computer Science: Software Development
2020-06 Auckland University of Technology (AUT)

2010-01 - High School Diploma

Contact

Address

22 Beverly Place New Lynn, Auckland, 1010

Phone

0274982366

E-mail

Johnageronimo1@gmail.co m

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Software Development Control: GitHub

Wireframes

WordPress

React JS

Microsoft word, Excel, and PowerPoint

Agile environment - SCRUM

IT Project Management

Database Management

Meetings

Php, Java, C

Play musically within a band for small or big scale events